One developer wrote this skill that actually gave access to production
credentials to the agents.
And this was not kind of paved path.
You know, these credentials were not kind of
just in time, nicely injected, they were overly permissive.
And when our security team saw that developers are using a skill like that,
they freaked out. We found, I... 76.
I don't remember the exact number, skills that had purely malicious code.
So, malware.
The AI Native Dev is a podcast for developers and engineering
leads at the cutting edge of AI and agentic coding.
Join your hosts, Guy Podjarny and me, Simon Maple,
every week as we chat with the most exciting voices in
AI and tackle the biggest questions facing developers today.
This is the AI Native Dev.
Hello and welcome to
this special live stream with Tessl and Snyk in partnership.
So really, really happy for everyone to to to be here.
We have Krzysztof Huszcza, who is a product leader in AI security at Snyk.
Hopefully I got that right Chris. Yeah. Pretty good man.
Pretty good.
Yeah. Hey, guys. Good. Good to see you.
Good to. Good to hear you. And thank you for having me.
And, of course, we actually worked together for a good number of years.
Unfortunately, for years.
It was a happy time.
A day doesn't go by when I don't think about how amazing that team.
I forgot you as soon as well.
That's. That's good, that's good.
Well.
Welcome, Chris. Thanks for having me.
So today, tell us a little bit about what you what you do.
Product leader in AI security. What does that mean?
So I lead AI security incubation at Snyk.
Snyk is kind of traditionally an application security company.
But one of the things we want to, you know, get into
we we believe that's one of the biggest
opportunities in security going forward is agent security and AI security.
And for that we created like a, a, a, a group on the side,
kind of a little bit isolated from the core application security product.
And we're kind of running it more, more as an incubator.
And I'm incubating, a few things in that group,
a few products in kinda agent security, AI security space for Snyk.
Yeah. Amazing. Amazing.
So let's go back a little bit down
to, to to the good old days when life was a lot simpler.
Pre AI mainstream AI Snyk was of course
obviously always a developer security company right.
Very much pushing the the you know, getting developers
engaged and using security from an early stage.
Right.
Tell us about the
I guess more traditionally the code security platform that that Snyk has.
Right.
So so traditionally what Snyk tried to do was kind of this kind of shift
level developer security motion where we said, okay, like,
you know, security doesn't scale anymore without developer involvement.
So how do we get developers to kind of
jointly own security program together with the asset team?
And the whole platform was was all about collaboration, really.
You know, like, how do we get the security team to kind of
governance, application security program run application security program at scale.
So do all the code scanning, open source scanning, containers, scanning,
etc., etc., but also kind of close the loop with developers.
So get developers to fix, remediate, run that, and also get developers
to basically prevent vulnerabilities from going to production. Right.
So, you know, there's a lot of friction there between devs and security
to this day, right?
Remediation is a friction threat.
Modeling is a friction, blocking developers
from pushing code to production because it has a security issue.
It's a friction.
So really, the company was all about kind of removing that friction
and kind of empowering these two to collaborate.
Yeah, yeah. And let's bring that into current day then.
And it's actually quite funny
that we were talking about the recent past because Alan has noticed
there's a Sinclair Spectrum on the shelf behind us.
See what else you can see on the on the live stream.
But let's bring that into the today.
Now obviously AI people using AI
there are gently or you know, as an assistant and so forth.
It's it's very mainstream now right.
What additional challenges does that bring from a from a coding point of view?
So well, challenges and I think opportunities.
Yeah.
I think the, you know, the biggest challenge,
for this,
for these developers is okay, now, now we are using agents to, to to to code.
Right.
We have like additional artifacts that we are producing.
Some of them are in natural language right.
So how do we secure those.
So we'll talk about skills in a sack. Right.
That's kind of different right.
Like the the traditional scanners don't really work with this.
I think the other one very interesting
one that is not yet a challenge, but soon will be a challenge is,
you know, instead of kind of coding, I'm already prompting.
Right. LLM is generating the code.
That code might be insecure,
pulling insecure dependencies or generating just vulnerabilities, right?
So that's that's that's happening today.
Maybe you have, you know,
like your PR check code scanning, or maybe you have code scanning.
After the agent generates code, you run a code scan.
So that's solved.
But but very soon what will happen is like you kind of move I, I believe that
I mean, I don't know when this will happen,
but I kind of firmly believe that,
that the developer workflows are fundamentally changing.
So very soon you will need to keep up with your agent, right?
So now you shift the problem from reviewing code.
So to I'm managing a team of agents.
And how do I really stay on top of what these agents are doing
when I'm kind of vibe coding using my agents, I'm already struggling.
Right.
So like, what changes are they making to my application?
So these are the kind of new challenges from, for from, from the developer
point of view is, you know, like how does the security fit in
with this new kind of developer workflow where developer is managing
a team of agents instead of just reviewing every single line of code?
What does the security tool even look like in this new era?
And it's interesting because when you look at
just the sheer volume of code that's generated and created,
of course there are going to be similar coding issues because agents
and llms have learned from our previous code in their training data,
and as a result,
they'll they'll essentially replicate a lot of what they they have seen.
And the next thing is, when you talk about a developer looking after
a team of agents, that team of agents, we need to provide them guidance.
We need to provide them almost like an onboarding to allow them
to build that code the way we want them to build that.
And it's it's become well accepted now that the best form
of of that guidance, providing that guidance is through context.
Right.
And let's let's talk a little bit about context, because obviously
one of the probably I would say the two main ways of providing context
is either you're writing into the agent's MD or into the Claude, MD, for example.
Another way is to be able to say, look, I want to I want to create a skill,
a piece of markdown that I can progressively disclose to my agent.
So I provide that skill that my agent knows the name and description.
For example, when the agent has a task that it feels
it needs that skill, it will load that skill in.
Now these skills are designed to be reused, so I
if I use a skill, I could share it to you or the rest of my organization.
Or I can put that on GitHub and other people can kind of like download that.
I've said a bunch whereby there's a million security threats already.
So let's talk a little bit about, let's talk a little bit
about how the, the, the context that we're talking
can and let's start with skills can actually contain further issues.
And perhaps we talk a little bit about your toxic skills
report and research that you did earlier this year.
Yeah. Yeah.
So we did, we did, we did research this topic I think in March.
So, so a while ago.
And I think it was about at the same time,
you know, OpenClaw was basically exploding.
Right.
So, so OpenClaw got released and then there was a huge kind of
community motion to kind of contribute to that repository,
including huge community motion to push skills to, to ClawHub.
And that's where we kind of went.
And we analyzed, you know, like the skills that that people pushed.
And of course, because this was such a big moment for the entire community.
And, you know, like one of the probably foundational moments of agentic
development, right, like OpenClaw, we found a lot of problems there.
So so this is mainly kind of for third party
skills that other developers are pushing.
And you want to go and reuse.
Which makes sense.
You know, the use case is, is is very clear.
Like I don't want to reinvent like the same as open source.
I don't want to reinvent the wheel, you know,
like if there is a skill that helps me to or helps my agent to do front end
applications or, I don't know, connect to slack and again,
customer data, whatever, whatever that is. Right?
You you like you you you publish you you want to reuse that?
But when we analyzed, this, these skills
on the OpenClaw repository, we found a lot of problems.
Right.
So, we found, I think, 70, 76.
I don't remember the exact number, skills that had purely malicious code.
So, malware.
So skills, as you probably know, folks, is, partially,
you know, the, the file, the MD file that gives instruction to the agent.
But skills can also contain code, right?
So kind of the first attack vector, if you are using third party
skills is somebody just puts malware there.
And then basically your agents or your, your,
your coding agents takes that and executes that, that, that malware.
Right.
So so we found 70 odd instances of of people putting malware there.
And that's extremely hard to detect from a normal, like a regular tool,
traditional tool, because this code may not even run.
It's just, it's
but it's influencing an agent to be able to build code that can run and actually,
you know, do bad things.
Right? Yeah. Exactly. Exactly.
So that's that's that's, that's one the other one
that kind of traditional tools don't detect is the, the kind
that the natural language part right of the, of the skill.
So, you know, you can put, put prompt injection
there and then, you know, that gets into the agent context.
Agents are not very good at distinguishing between
your instruction and context that is passed through third parties.
So these prompt injection attacks, are very kind of common, like,
doable to, to, to kind of trick the agent, overtake the agent,
and then basically do whatever, whatever you want. Right.
Like it's, it's, it's pretty much like if you manage to overtake,
the agent, it's, you know, like, you can filter it credentials from the,
from the environment where the agent is running.
And then, you know, that's a very serious attack vector.
Right.
So so we found a bunch of skills there as well that contained prompt injections.
And again this is not something that a traditional security scanner
would would find right.
Like you need to basically create a new scanner, a new new tool
to analyze natural language and have this kind of classifier
that classifies whether whether natural language is
a potential prompt injection called contains prompt injection,
basically contains instructions to overtake overtake the agent.
So we did that and and yeah we found we found a bunch of those as well.
Yeah.
And so like you know obviously there's a ton of,
you know big organizations out there that wants to adopt,
you know, agent flows and the usage of agents.
And they want to make sure that this guidance is provided to their
to their skills, sorry,
to provide it to their agents through skills and other context.
It's actually very similar.
You kind of like mentioned
like a connection there between how we think about skills and context
and also libraries.
And yes, there is malicious content context, and there's
malicious libraries that can be shared in a very, very similar way.
What can a developer actually do to make sure that any skills
that they download, you know, is, is, first of all, safe, right.
And how can an organization better adopt such technology.
Right.
With, with with that in with that governance in mind.
So, one of the common things that people do is kind of host this skill registries.
Right.
And Tessl is one, one. Of of hurts.
I've heard of a skills registry.
Yeah. So tell us about that.
What is the skills registry.
So I so two in the wild you probably know more actually.
So so, you can you can,
you can tell for the folks as well, but I think kind of two in the wild.
Right?
So one is just like, more of a
free for all open source community kind of skill registry where, like,
everybody can just put skills and, you know, you make them searchable and,
and then you can basically download, these skills to your laptop.
I don't know, I'm using a lot of skills.
Every time I, I'm doing something, related to front end,
there is an entropic front end design skill.
Right. I'm using that.
So, so the
kind of like, people publish these skills and.
Yeah, like an important thing there is, because there are third party,
so they are untrusted is to, to make sure that you have some sort of security
scan running
as the skill is already published and kind of as part of the, of the registry.
Right.
Because if you download the skill and you, you,
you scan it after downloading might actually be game over.
Maybe not.
But you know, like if this skill contains malware,
I mean, you don't want to be downloading malware to your to your laptop, right?
So it's a very important kind of feature that, you know, like we are helping Tessl
with for for your registry is is kind of this, this skill scanning capability.
So like as you're downloading you can check
the skill is verified by a security vendor and it doesn't contain anything,
anything dangerous.
So that's kind of one part of 111, one type of, of, of registries.
The other is more of an internal enterprise.
So as I'm talking to enterprise customers, more and more of them are actually
as they are going through this agent transformation,
they are hosting their own kind of skill, skill registries.
So I know a platform team would have like a paved path for developers to push.
Stuff to production. Right?
They want to kind to expose that paved path to the agent through some context.
So they create a skill, they push that skill,
and they ask developers to use that skill whenever agent is
is pushing stuff to production. Right.
So then then then that becomes like a common pattern for, for a lot
of companies to, to, to operate and share skills across, across employees.
And they're actually, I think, security scanning
is still useful before skills are being, being deployed.
But actually the attack vectors are slightly different, right?
Because it's no longer third party.
So somebody who you don't trust, it's your own developers pushing these skills.
So I think what you want to kind of ensure there is more around
our developers doing something that they shouldn't be doing right.
As a secure.
So so an example that happened internally at Snyk.
One developer wrote this skill
that actually gave access to production credentials to the agents.
And this was not kind of paved path.
You know,
these credentials were not kind of just in time, nicely injected,
they were, they were overly permissive.
And when our security team saw that developers are using a skill like that,
they freaked out right? Immediately. Right.
So so there
you you basically want to ensure some standards and make sure that the skills
that you're publishing, you know,
like developers know what these skills are exposing their agents to,
but also they are saying, right, I think that's that's what I would say.
Yeah. So there's a lot to break down there.
And I think, why don't we start with kind of like,
why don't we go through a little bit around the,
the Tessl and Snyk partnership and kind of like break down
some of the things that,
you know, developers will want to do with such a registry
and how that can help folks
from a security point of view and a governance point of view.
So, so one of the things
that was announced a number of months ago was, was the, the,
the integration of Snyk scans for context into the Tessl registry.
And what that means is people who add their context, their skills into the Tessl
registry will automatically get a Snyk scan on that skill.
And what that allows people, developers and folks to do to see is where
potential security issues like the things that you mentioned with,
with the, with the, with the prompt injection and so forth,
it provides people with an understanding that actually
there could be a prompt injection here, even if there wasn't one that was meant.
For example, maybe it's pointing to some third party
site or some some, you know, doing a web search.
There could be the potential for,
for a direct or indirect prompt injection there to, to exist through that.
So it's about, you know, giving people that insight into, into what exists.
One of the other key things that I think is potentially a security issue
is a developer downloading a skill that is maybe absolutely fine,
a new version becoming available, or at least a different
an update occurring to that skill.
I'm actually where there are no versions, you actually pulling down,
you know, an updated skill or the wrong version of the skill
without even realizing there's a potential malicious issue there.
So I think associating scans with versions is super important as well.
So that's some of the things that we,
that we've added
into, into Tessl with skill versioning
and then the ability to have those skills scanned.
Bye bye bye, Snyk.
Let's talk a little bit about a secure
by default agent stack and what that looks like.
What would you say from the from a developers point of view?
Let's start with the developer.
And maybe we kind of like lean into other other groups there from a
from a developers point of view there, there they have whatever
a coding platform of their choice on their machine.
They want to use some skills.
What are some of the best practices that a developer should do today,
and how close are we to that secure by default?
Oh, I don't you know, it's it's an emerging field.
I don't think anybody that you know has a has has the answer to that.
So for skill specifically and to kind of devs,
I think it's extremely useful to, well,
third party skills of course, like scan right before, before you use them.
But also
when you are authoring your own skills, like running it through a security scanner
just to tell you potentially what this skill is doing.
Could be a useful feedback.
So just to give you an example, right.
I was writing this skill to download data from slack.
Right.
And then I, I run it through a security scanner before I pushed.
So I have kind of this pre-COVID hook where like I, I, I,
I integrated our own security scanner and before I push to GitHub, you know,
like I, I ran the security scanner and it tells me, hey, you know, like this,
this slack data that, that you're downloading might have prompt injection.
I'm like, okay, you know, like it's my slack, right?
Maybe it's not a big attack vector, so I shouldn't worry.
But I did tell my agent, okay.
Hey, like,
just put some basic kind of protections against prompt injection in the skill.
So that's kind of, you know, like you you have this kind of feedback from,
from a security scanner.
And then the agent,
you kind of ask your agent to basically improve the skill
based on, based on that feedback.
I think that is super useful.
I think it's super useful.
Also on the on the quality perspective,
I think this is something that you folks are are working on, right?
Like, I think the biggest problem I have as a developer when I,
when I write my own skills, like these skills initially are very personal.
Right.
So I have this actually like to,
to write a personal skill for me to do a workflow.
Super easy. Right?
I just
I just talk to the agent, I do the workflow once
and then I after after the session, like I'm ending the session, I say, okay,
hey, you write a skill for me
so we can repeat the same workflow and I save the skill.
But then when I want to share that with other people,
that is much more tricky because now I want the skill to generalize, right?
So now I'm kind of getting into the how do I make a high quality
skill that is shareable across my, you know, company.
Right. And and that's where I need help personally.
Right.
From from folks like you to kind of help me, you know, like basically get
get the skill in shape and, and make sure that this skill
is in the right shape to, to share it with my or my peers.
It generalizes.
So it's not specific to my workflow.
So I, I think this kind of, workflows are still emerging.
But that's what I'm doing personally with with skills.
Yeah. Yeah.
And I'd love to work at about maybe five minutes or so left
and then we'll jump into some some questions.
I'd love to hear if folks have questions online, let us know.
Let us know about any questions that you have either.
Kind of like,
you know,
the Snyk security scanning, the Tessl registry or a combination of the two,
and we'll cover that in just a few minutes.
But I think that's a there's a there's a couple
of really interesting things that you kind of like mentioned.
One is the almost like the how good is my skill, which is all about evals.
And I think those evals will change depending on if I'm using something
personally or add other other scenarios in for the wider for the wider usage.
And it's absolutely key that we do nail down those security issues before
before sharing.
One other thing is when we, as we do,
share that out
and we'll kind of like talk
one step higher now instead of the developer
maybe thinking a little bit about more governance.
It's about almost like identifying if I was to share this to my team,
how do I protect my entire team for for downloading less secure context.
And I think this is where you can potentially use Tessl with Snyk here
to to run, or at least
on a on an installation of context.
You can use the Snyk score as a threshold to to give
developers guidance on whether they should or shouldn't install this skill.
Right. 100%.
I think we have to do more work on this site here
because like initially when we when we did skills, we assumed, you know,
this third party skills and the scanner was kind of more concerned about around
malicious third parties are, publishing stuff online.
How do we protect people
from not downloading malware or prompt injection, etc., etc.?
I think, again, I think I said that before, but it it is slightly different,
kind of a set of things that you want to check if you want to
give developer feedback on security of their own skills,
or give the team feedback on security of the skill that they are downloading
so they know what they are exposing their agents to.
Right?
So for example, not adding some lethal trifecta, you know,
like style, kind of exposure to the agent
or the agent can potentially get prompt injected and exfiltrate data.
So I think that's, that's a that's kind of like a good, you know,
like stuff that we will focus on in the future very soon.
And hopefully also has a continuation of this partnership is
how do we make it useful for developers when they write skills to understand
that they are doing the right things from the security perspective?
Right.
So the kind of feedback loop to developers and again, like as an example,
you know, like the the, the security incident that we had ourselves,
you know, like if you're a developer and you are hard coding secrets, of course
that's bad, but also like mishandling secrets and, you know,
like basically the agent is is told to pass secrets in plaintext.
That's an example, right?
If you if your skill can perform
a destructive action on some production environment.
Right.
So kind of this, this, this, this feedback where you basically understand
potential consequences of the skill that you are developing
yourself is, kind of next focus for us for sure.
And, and,
and a very exciting kind of opportunity to, to also collaborate with you folks.
Yeah, absolutely.
So, we're going to go to questions in just a second.
I want to I want to ask though, there's a, there's a, there's a new product.
That Snyk is going to be GA'ing.
Yeah. That's true, in a few days. Right.
Fingers crossed, few days. Yeah.
Can you tell us a little bit about that?
Can you give us a sneak preview?
Right.
So, so our next focus in, in the kind of AI
agent agent security incubation lab under the umbrella of Evo.
So Evo is our kind of product umbrella for for for for for the next generation
of Snyk products is a what we call a coding agent security product.
That is aimed to secure coding agents.
So the problem that we are trying to, to solve is,
enterprises are rolling out these coding agents.
And sometimes, you know, the, security team is blocking the rollout, right?
So the platform team is coming to us and saying like, hey,
I cannot roll out these coding agents because the CSO said that there's no way
without any security guarantees, right?
On the other hand, sometimes, you know, the rollout happened
and they're trying to play catch up and calling us over the weekend and saying
like, hey, you know, like the, the, the, the agents got rolled out,
you know, and and security was not in the loop. Right.
So what we're trying to really enable is kind of empower the security teams
to secure these coding agents at scale without impacting agent productivity.
So that's also an important aspect for us because you can just block all network
traffic, right? And call it a day.
But then like basically the agent becomes useless. Right?
So so the three things very quickly that we are releasing here is supply chain
security for the agent.
So ability for you to govern.
See what skills and MCP servers your developers are using
that scales across all of your endpoints and and machines etc.
and and kind of perform risk assessment of these skills
and MCP servers and then create policies around MCP server
shouldn't be using personal access tokens, etc., etc..
So that's kind of on the supply chain, government
agent, supply chain governance, the output of the agent.
So the our our our core business, you know, code security
but now kind of integrated within the agent loop where agent is
generating code or downloading an open source library.
Just make sure that it's secure,
write the code that is generating is secure and fix it.
And then the third one that that that we're gonna release in open preview. But
hopefully kind of GA in Q3 is
and guides railing the agent behavior so that, that that one is,
is probably the most kind of right now urgent for all a lot of security teams.
How do I actually make sure that the agent is not leaking credentials?
How do I how do I make sure that the agent is not misbehaving,
not having prompt injections?
Not not, you know, leaking credentials, etc..
Right.
So, so so those three are, are kind of the things that we are working on
and releasing. Very excited about that. Awesome, awesome.
Let's look through some of the, some of the questions.
We have one question in from from YouTube with regards to Tessl registry.
If you use it as a private workspace, you don't get the same UI experience
as the main pages with score, tile, Snyk, score, etc.
so with with the Tessl registry you'll actually get,
you will get the the quality score, the impact score, and the
and the Snyk score for both public or private plugins.
If it's a local plugin, I believe you won't get the
you won't get the Snyk score, so you need it published to the Tessl registry.
But if it's private or public, you should still get that.
The difference?
For those who who haven't heard of our workspaces,
a workspace is essentially a space in which you can upload your plugins
and skills to, and you can create you can mark that as private or public.
If it's public, anyone can access that on the internet.
If it's private, you will need a Tessl account
that has access to that workspace in order to see that plugin.
But you should see all Snyk score and tile scores and things like that.
Additionally, regards to utilizing the Tessl plugins within different agents,
how does your plugin format fit into codecs for example?
So if we were to if we were to think about agents
and this is
this is an interesting question because agents of course
all have their different formats and things like that.
The way you would install a plugin if you were comfortable with its security
posture and the Snyk scan and things like that, you would install that plugin
and that plugin will be installed into the Tessl folder of your project.
You will also have a whole ton of different dot folders
that will be a Claude, a Codex or Gemini, etc., etc.
those will have an indirect links
to the Tessl folder and
as a result, any agent that you load from that or that you run from that,
from that project will automatically have all of those skills accessible.
Do you find much difference between the different
the different agents from a security point of view,
or is it pretty much more in the in the skills itself?
I suppose it's the wording I suspect.
Yeah, I think I, I not really.
The only difference is that some of them
support hooks, some of them don't support hooks. Right.
But kind of codecs and cloud codes and cursor are like
the the three that we focus on and kind of have the widest adoption.
And between these three, like it's it's very similar.
So but it's important to, to have tools that work across all of them.
So you like, like yours. Right.
So you don't need to kind of go
to the path of installing for like the, the same thing for, for each agent.
Right.
So project level skills a really good idea.
Yeah, yeah. Awesome.
Awesome.
Awesome. We only have 30s minute left.
I don't want to wrap up by asking one final question.
Okay. What?
Let's ask, what one piece of advice would you give today to an agent developer
to improve their security posture, particularly when it comes to
a to a context point of view, I suspect.
Oh, One piece of advice I would give.
Don't don't go
yolo, I think I, I don't know, that's the one that comes to my mind.
I think, I think a lot of deaths are, you know, like, just they
they are there, they are kind of playing with this technology, right?
This new technology. And you want
you want to kind of understand how it works.
And and it's very kind.
It's very simple to just, you know, auto approve or all actions,
just download skills just like don't don't do it right.
Like don't go YOLO. Like just just just think through.
Like what what your what you're actually doing.
Like the same like, attackers are, very interested in this field.
Right. These attacks.
On on coding agent and and different variants are not theoretical.
They are happening in the wild.
Right?
So, use sandboxing,
don't auto approve and check your skills
and use kind of trusted registries like Tessl, like, don't go.
YOLO is probably my my my, my my simple.
All about building that trust and automating.
When you have that trust. This right.
So so the tools are emerging. Right.
So the tools will help you out.
Will have you will have you, kind of covered.
Right.
Like, Tessl Snyk and other tools that in, in this space, but in very often
like the tools are not there yet. Right.
Like, it's
not easy, for example, to run as, like, a fully sandboxed agent today, right?
So just, make sure that you, you, you don't go fully all on, on,
on, on everything you do and you don't fully kind of
just just just think like, don't outsource thinking to your agent.
Just think for yourself what you're doing. Right.
That's a and use the tools as much as possible.
Amazing Chris, thank you very much.
It's been a pleasure to thank you so much to chat.
And and thank you all for listening.
Thank you for the questions.
If you wanted to learn more about the integration between Tessl
and Snyk, do you go to Tessl IO Forward Registry?
And from there, you'll be able to see a whole ton of skills
that automatically have Snyk running on,
and you'll be able to see the security guidelines and instructions as to as to
what is it about the each skill which is potentially causing complications.
Do also go to Snyk IO and check out their scanners there as well,
and also stay tuned in the next few days to see that GA product release.
Thank you. Thank you very much. Thank you for that.
Bye for now.
The AI Native Dev is brought to you by Tessl, the package manager for skills and context.
Your hosts are Guy Podjarny and me, Simon Maple.
Our producer is Tom Dowler.
The AI Native Dev is not just a podcast, it's a community.
And we host monthly meetups at the Tessl offices in central London.
Visit Tessl IO forward slash community to learn more and I hope to see you there.